ultrasabers.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy | Ultra Sabers

We at Ultra Sabers are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to both websites we own and operate: www.ultrasabers.com and www.saberforum.com. Our Privacy Policy dictates usage of any data collection through use of our websites or business engagement. In compliance with GDPR, our policy has been updated to identify and describe access to, and the ability to modify your personal information.

Please note: If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use or engage with the Websites.

Changes or updates to our privacy policy may be found here, and this page will always remain public for your reference.

Please direct any questions regarding our privacy policy or use of any information you may have provided to us to Info@UltraSabers.com

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

### Information We Collect When You Visit our Websites

You are free to explore our Websites without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you wish to make a purchase or engage with our Websites, you will be prompted to provide any and all required personal information about yourself.

“Personal Information” refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us at any time during a transaction or otherwise, that identifies you as an individual. This can be anything from your contact information (Name, e-mail address, company name, address, or phone number) as well as other information about yourself or your business.

In addition, personal information may also include behavioral information or payment information associated to your use of our websites. Behavioral information refers to information about your computer or device, and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed.

  * We collect personal or behavioral information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information.
  * We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
  * Like most websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our email newsletter are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy.

### Use of Personal Information

In addition to any application or uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, an “Unsubscribe” link is included in the footer of any email received from our sites. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and ‘members-only’ content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

### Use of Behavioral Information

We collect and observe behavioral information from users in order to improve our websites. Behavioral information may be analyzed alone or in combination with personal information when possible, in order to provide you with personalized information or promotions.

### Product reviews & service testimonials

Product reviews & customer testimonials are collected through a third party program to maintain honesty and accuracy. Reviews submitted to this service are then displayed on our websites by including a first name and last initial alongside the content of the review & rating.

### Use of Credit Card Information

Payment information is used solely for the collection of payment from you in regards to your order or its modification. Payments are collected through a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT VISITOR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures & technologies to maintain and protect the safety of your personal information from any unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to maintain confidentiality of your information. All pages of our site is protected via an up to date Secure Socket Layer (SSL), and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

## Social Media Features

Our websites utilize common social media integrations, such as the Facebook “Like” button. Use of these integrations may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media integrations are hosted directly on our websites, however, your interactions with these features are also governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the social media companies integrated with them.

### External Websites

Our websites my often provide links to numerous other websites or entities. We do not control, and are cannot be held responsible for, any content, tracking, or other practices of these other websites. Links found on our website does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices, and will be included for reference only. The extent of this privacy policy does not extend beyond ultrasabers.com or saberforum.com, and as such cannot apply to these other websites. Engagement with them subjects your information to any privacy or other policies they may have.

## Retention of Personal Information

How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, and the duration of which will restart with each engagement of the website.

Personal information obtained through purchase through our site is retained in your account and preserved indefinitely, as it may include purchase history, or reward points associated to the account. Behavioral data obtained through cookies and on-site tracking as mentioned above may be retained for up to 540 days, at which time, your information will be no longer accessible to us and will be either deleted or anonymized.

We retain Personal Information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, as long as is required in order to contact you regarding your order or our other services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements).

If you have signed up for our newsletter, we will retain personal information as well as your marketing preferences through the use of our mailing integration. This information can be removed through the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email.

## DO WE DISCLOSE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We Never Sell Personal Information.  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term “outside parties” does not include Ultra Sabers LLC. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Google Chrome, FireFox, or Safari) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

### Advertising

We partner with a number of third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.

A notification was provided on your first visit to the site that would allow you to opt in or out of allowing us to present you with ads. If you are in the European Union and wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>. Please note this does not opt you out of being served all advertising, and you may continue to receive generic ads depending on the website or platforms your are browsing. Please allow 24-48 hours for updates to be processed and populated.

## HOW CAN YOU OPT-OUT, REMOVE OR MODIFY INFORMATION YOU HAVE PROVIDED TO US?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the “My Account” section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the “My Account” section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

You may also request access, correction, updates or deletion of your personal information at any time by emailing info@UltraSabers.com. We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.

### You have the following data protection rights:

You may request access, correction, updates or deletion of your personal information by contacting us at info@ultrasabers.com.

If we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

To take action of any of these rights, you must contact us at info@ultrasabers.com, or by mail to:

Ultra Sabers  
308 West Edgewood Dr  
Friendswood, TX 77546  
Phone: (832) 569-5194

We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.

## Questions and feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.

## Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.ultrasabers.com/terms.asp) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Saberforum.com disclaimer:

Be aware that any information disclosed through the use of and engagement of the front-end of our public message boards/ forum may be seen and collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Websites if requested.

Updated May, 2018
